I, Grace, have a dream!
It's to surround myself with hot guys
and spend the rest of my life
living comfortably on Santorini Island.
And in order to do that...
I've gathered intel, put it to use,
and then killed, killed,
and killed some more!
Now, finally, my long-awaited dream
is almost within my grasp.
And she is the key.
If I can take Xue's head...
I'll be living the good life!
You just wait,
Xue.
Um... Ms. Yuki...
I can't fall asleep if you keep
staring at me like that.
Episode 5: What You Want to Protect.
But we have no way of knowing when that
scoundrel will next appear, Master Hitoyoshi.
Furthermore...
Even a moment's lapse of attention on my part
could be enough for her to dismember you.
I'm getting cut up into pieces now?
That is why, until I can find out
more about that woman,
I would like to be your bodyguard.
Seriously? I really don't think I can sleep
like this, so is there any other way?
Then allow me to suggest a more
sleep-friendly option, Master Hitoyoshi.
What?
Lending you my lap would restrict my movement,
but please allow me to share your bed.
Ugh... Why can't I just say no?!
Anyway, I'm more worried about you, Ms. Yuki.
She's more likely to be here
for you than for me.
For me... For me?
What's she so self-conscious
about all of a sudden?
If I were to be attacked while asleep
by someone of her level,
I'd be able to handle it,
with one hand at that.
With one hand...
During the day, I only had
one small knife with me,
so I'm glad I was able to scare her off.
O-Oh, so that's what you were doing.
I'm certain even she isn't foolish
enough to attack me directly.
Is Ms. Yuki actually really strong?
I have no idea how she found out about me.
It seems my past is catching up with me.
And now I've involved you.
But do not worry, Master Hitoyoshi.
This is my foremost area of specialty.
I will protect you,
no matter what happens.
As the one who taught me what kindness is,
you are a very important person to me.
S-Still, I can't help
but worry about you, Ms. Yuki.
I know there's nothing I can do,
but I don't want to lose you, either.
Very well. I will bear that in mind.
It's getting a little hot in here.
I'm gonna open a window.
I will open it for you, just in case.
We cannot discount the possibility of a sniper.
Is this what it's like for VIPs
with bodyguards, too?
Oh... I-I smell Katsuda's Sauce...
Huh? Are the neighbors having
a midnight snack or something?
No... This is...
Judging from the direction of the wind,
the scent is coming from
the front gate of this house!
There's no mistaking it!
You've certainly lost your touch, Xue.
It's not like you to fall
for an easy trap like this.
You're so distracted by this pretend family
of yours that you're making dumb mistakes.
I can't believe they used to call you
the White Wolf of the Dragon's Nine.
Now, now. Not so fast.
You know even you can't kill me
before I put this kid's eyes out.
So be a good girl and...
...You.
Do you understand what will happen to you
if you lay so much as a finger on him?
I will make you suffer so much,
you'll wish for a death that never comes.
So, are you ready to accept
the consequences of your actions?
I-I see. It seems the White Wolf
hasn't completely lost her fangs yet.
Well, the truth is, I have business with you.
It's a very important matter.
I simply must end your life.
But with my strength alone, I wouldn't be
able to kill you, even in a thousand years.
So I'll be borrowing this boy
for just a little while.
Come to the school tonight at 2 AM.
I'll guarantee his safety until then.
You were born to kill people.
The stench of death forever clings to you.
No matter how much you deny it,
you will always be Xue.
I know. I know, Mentor.
If he'd never met me, Master Hitoyoshi
wouldn't have had to face such danger.
After all, this was a fleeting dream
from the start.
You have the composure of one
who doesn't see people as people—
a brutal killer.
There is no other way for you to live.
I will kill that woman
and eliminate all traces of what happened.
After I've ensured Master Hitoyoshi's safety,
I will leave the country,
and everything will resolve itself.
And then I will simply return to living as Xue.
Without me in the picture...
Without me?
I know there's nothing I can do,
but I don't want to lose you, either.
No, that's not right.
What I... What I wish for is...
The thing I want is...
Ogiso Private High School
Yep.
All done!
Looking good!
Being strung up really suits you.
Like heck it does!
You're right. Now that I think about it,
you'd look great in bondage.
Wanna give it a try next time?
Pick a kink and stick with it!
Hey, aren't you afraid?
Huh?
I have your tiny little life in the palm
of my hand right now, you know?
A life so insignificant that if I decided
on a whim to crush it,
it'd be gone, just like that.
And you only have your Ms. Yuki to blame!
How does it feel to have your life
in danger because of that woman?
Don't you hate her?
Aren't you sad?
Aren't you disappointed?
No. To be honest, I'm really
scared right now, but...
Ms. Yuki told me she'd protect me.
And the only thing I can do
right now is believe in her.
Hm...
How boring!
You've got more guts than I thought.
Even though you look like a hamster.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
Not just anyone can tame Xue.
In truth, I couldn't care less
whether you live or die.
I just want to kill Xue with my own hands.
Sorry in advance if you get
killed in the crossfire, 'kay?
You're scarier when you
talk like that, you know.
And you keep mentioning this "Xue"...
Is that Ms. Yuki?
Huh?
You were with Xue all this time
without knowing her true identity?
All I know is that she's a maid
and former assassin.
That's it?!
She's...
That woman...
is a monster.
I used to share my corner of the world
with lots of real dangerous folk,
but Xue was special even amongst them.
She was a ruthless murderer with no mercy
for anyone—a butcher who lived only to kill.
The fourth of the Dragon's Nine:
Xue the White Wolf.
Th-The Dragon's Nine?
The most powerful clan of assassins in the world. They gather talented individuals
from various countries and train them.
It's said that they're behind
every major shakeup in history.
But, precisely because they are
such a powerful organization,
there are many groups who oppose them!
Put simply, if I can take the head of one
of their members—in other words, Xue—
my reputation will skyrocket!
I'll be able to get the real good gigs—the high-
paying stuff—and make my dream come true!
Hmm...
Um... Who are we talking about again?
Like I said, I'm talking about Ms. Yuki.
The Ms. Yuki I know
is a supposedly 16-year-old high school girl
who jumps and falls a lot,
is completely expressionless in one moment
but super emotional in the next,
naïve by nature but with a love for
tonkatsu sauce unmatched by anyone...
I couldn't believe it either!
At first, I thought it was just
someone who looked like her,
so I observed her for about three weeks,
but there's no doubt that she's Xue!
The White Wolf of the Dragon's Nine!
When you guys were talking
about marriage on the porch,
I thought about just shooting
you both, there and then!
Oh, uh... That conversation
just kinda got out of hand.
Stop blushing!
I sort of understand now.
There's something off about you.
No normal person would be able
to stay calm in a situation like this,
let alone carry on a conversation with
someone who was prepared to kill them.
There's something about him that isn't normal.
Something that was able to thaw
Xue's ice-cold heart of a killer.
But that's even better for me!
People become weaker the more invested
they are in protecting something.
Everyone knows that.
And no one in our trade would be naïve
enough not to take advantage of it.
Assassins aren't honor-bound by rules.
And that's why even I have a path to victory!
Come to me, monster.
Become the first stepping stone
on the road to my dreams!
Cutting bullets in half as you run?
What is this, an action movie?
But that's...
nothing I can't handle!
One well-done maid, coming right up!
Whaddaya call this? "Better watch your step"?
No... Ms. Yuki!
My, did I overdo it a bit?
Well, I'm sure it'll take more than
one measly trap to kill Xue...
Oh, crap!
Ms. Yuki! I'm so glad you're okay!
I'm glad you are, too, Master Hitoyoshi!
I'll save you right away!
Ah, this sucks!
First you dodge my landmines,
and then you give me the cold shoulder?
That's not normal, you know,
Xue!
You sure are taking me lightly
by attacking me head-on, Xue.
Oh, I'm sorry, was it "Ms. Yuki" now?
I heard you kept your identity a secret,
but isn't that because you still feel guilty?
That's right, you're the great Xue,
the youngest member of the
Dragon's Nine in history!
If he found out who you really were,
you wouldn't be able to stay here anymore.
You wanted to be normal, was it?
There is no way you'd ever—
Are you quite finished talking?
Master Hitoyoshi has school tomorrow.
Staying up any later than this
would be bad for his health.
Let us finish as quickly as possible.
SNAP
MEOW
"Master Hitoyoshi," "Master Hitoyoshi"!
Is that all you have to say?
Ms. Yuki's
Happy Meal of Love
Right now, I am thinking of
Miss Riko and Agemochitaro.
Katsuda's Sauce is also constantly on my mind.
Why does she hold them in such high regard?!
Goodness. You certainly
are taking this lightly.
Is Ms. Yuki wary of something?
Oh, or is it...
that the great Xue is too cold-hearted
to mind the boy losing an arm or two?
Yikes!
Hey! I've still got some fun in store,
so don't rush it, 'kay?
L-Laser sniper rifles?!
That's right!
As you can see,
if you resist even a little bit,
dear Hitoyoshi here will be reduced to a torso!
So just behave and let me beat you to death—
Hey!
How can she just rush in
without a moment's hesitation?!
Xue the White Wolf
never lets her prey get away.
Ha! I see! Some "normal" you wanna be!
You didn't care one whit
about the boy's life to begin with!
You really had me going, you know!
If you want it that badly, I'll put some
nice, big holes into the boy's limbs...
so you can hang him up to decorate your room!
She used her knives to deflect the bullets?!
I screwed up by adding the laser sights
to make it more threatening!
No, nobody would expect a stunt
like that to even be possible!
But I'm not out of options yet!
CRACK
Mrow! My smartphone!
Member...
of the strongest clan of assassins,
Fourth of the Dragon's Nine...
This is Xue the White Wolf!
You lose.
Ugh!
Not good! Not good! She's going to kill me!
I have no choice but to create
an opening and make my escape!
You think you can just kill me
and live happily ever after?
No matter how much you try,
you'll never be Ms. Yuki!
You're Xue!
You know it more than anyone else!
You really are foolish, you know that?
No one just quits a job like ours—
the talented ones like you least of all!
Even if you kill me right now,
countless others will come after your head
to make a name for themselves.
Do you intend to kill all of them?
Is that what you consider "normal"?!
Ms. Yuki...
You're right...
That was my idea of "normal" until now.
The more I killed, the more recognition I got.
That was all I knew how to do.
I thought that was the only place I belonged.
But everything is different now.
I won't kill anyone anymore.
And I won't let anyone die
because of me, either!
No matter what happens from here on out,
I will do my best to protect the normal life
I obtained of my own free will!
Xue the White Wolf
never lets her prey get away.
She will chase them to the ends of Hell.
No matter where you hide, she will emerge
from the darkness to slit your throat.
The strongest, most horrible assassin...
Those rumors...
I thought they were tales told about her
exploits and methods of killing, but...
That's not it. She's probably just...
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
...a naïve, willful woman who won't
stop until she gets what she wants.
Just like back then...
and just now, as well.
So if she really wanted me dead,
she would have killed me a long time ago?
I really thought I was a goner!
Oh, man. I get to live after all.
Those two are really interesting!
Oh, boy. That was one thrilling day.
Well, I had faith that you'd come
and save me, Ms. Yuki.
Master Hitoyoshi.
I can't apologize enough for involving you
in such a perilous situation.
It is all my fault.
If it's what you desire, then...
I shall disappear from...
I shall... disappear from...
Hey, Ms. Yuki.
Please teach me some
self-defense techniques after this.
I'm supposed to be a man, you know?
So I want to be able to help you
at least a little, Ms. Yuki!
Yes! If you'll have me!